Is that so?
そうなの?
Yeah.
うん
tickles.
くすぐったい
It tickles so well.
あんまくすぐったい
wait a minute.
ちょっと 待って
It tickles my neck.
首くすぐったい
It doesn't go down that much.
そんなに下がられることないじゃん
what are you doing?
何をしているの?
no.
いや
There's a window behind me.
後ろは窓なんだけど
Aren't you scared?
怖くない?
Looks like below.
下みたい
It's not scary.
怖くはない
There might be someone watching.
見ている人いるかもね
Sit down for a moment.
ちょっと 腰かけて
The important thing is that there were various accidents.
大事はね、 いろいろとアクシデントがあった
Accident?
ア クシデント?
Before I arrived, I got caught on a train.
来る前にね、 電車で引っ掛けられちゃった
Shall I use the phone?
電 話使おうか
What are you doing?
何してんの?
Nothing suits me.
何も似合わないよ
It smells good.
いい匂いする
picture?
え?
lie?
嘘?
What won't you do?
何しないよ
what?
何?
amazing.
すごい
what?
何?
You're a little sweaty.
ちょっと汗まんでるね
lie?
嘘?
Isn't that a lie?
嘘でしょ?
Sexy.
セクシーな
amazing.
すごい
something.
何か
Looks like it's going to fall.
落ちそう
It's a little unbalanced.
ちょっとバランスが悪い
Will it go up?
上がる?
It's going up though.
上がるけど
上がるけどね
It will break anyway.
とりあえず破けちゃう
Will it break?
破けちゃう?
It's torn, right?
破けてるでしょ?
It broke though.
破けちゃったけど
Where did you touch it?
どこ触った?
warm.
温かい
It's not warm.
温かくない
I have a body temperature though.
体温はあるけど
It's warm.
温かいじゃん
warm.
温かい
What are you doing?
何してんの?
Can it be torn?
破ける?
It can't be torn at all.
全然破けない
amazing.
すごい
It's sturdy.
頑丈だ
what are you doing?
何をしているの?
Wait, wait.
待って待って
I'm torn.
ビリビリしてる
It wasn't torn.
破けたじゃないし
Why are you tearing it up?
何で破いてるの?
Return.
返りさ
返り
Isn't it obvious?
当 た り前でしょ?
This has arrived.
これ入ってきたんだよ
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
what are you doing?
何してるの?
Torn.
ビリビリ
what?
何?
tear?
破 れる?
It's hard.
硬いね
I bought one that won't tear.
破れないやつを買ったんだ
It's not cheap.
安物じゃないね
安物じゃないよ
Wouldn't it be a problem if you went out for a while and it broke?
ちょっと 出かけて破れちゃったら困るでしょ?
Because it didn't break at all.
全然破けなかったから
I don't want to tear it up.
破いたいのないじゃん
It won't break.
破 れないんだよ
I bought one that wouldn't tear, so that's fine.
破けないの買ったんだもん、ちゃんと
Would you like to write it?
書いてみる?
What is that?
何のあれなの?
Is it a sexual fetish or something?
性癖とかそういうあれなの?
Is this okay?
これでいいの?
I can't see it that way.
それじゃ見えないよ
Isn't it embarrassing?
だって恥ずかしいでしょ?
No one can see that you're embarrassed.
恥ずかしいって誰も見てないよ
Isn't that the problem?
そういう問題じゃないの?
Are you taking that long?
そんなにじっくりにいる?
Hurry up.
早くして
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
what are you doing?
何してるの?
Look here.
こっち見て
lie?
嘘?
The meat is very dirty.
めっちゃ肉汚い
what are you doing?
何してるの?
There isn't.
無いよ
I don't think it's common.
普通は無いと思う
I'm getting cuter than you.
あんたよりかわいくなってくね
A little important.
ちょっと大切
It's about time I chewed it.
そろそろチューしちゃった
what?
何?
What is this hand?
この手は何?
what?
何?
Are you wearing anything underneath?
何か下も着てる?
Because I have to wear something cold.
だって寒いの着ないと
Hide it.
隠して
The one I have will break.
持ってるの割れちゃう
Thick.
分厚い
I'm on my way.
かけついてる
Take off your skirt.
スカートを脱いで
Are you going to take off your bottom too?
下も脱ぐの?
Yo
よ
Yes.
い しょ
I took it off.
脱いだ
cold.
寒い
It's so cold.
めちゃめちゃ寒い
cold?
寒い?
cold.
寒い
My hands were warm.
手が温かかった
Because I'm spilling it.
こぼしてるから
Don't look at me too seriously.
あんまマジマジと見ないで
It's not a story you do while in love, right?
恋しながらする話じゃないでしょ、
absolute.
絶対
You took it off.
外したでしょ
I noticed.
気づいた
Because the thing on my back is gone.
だって背中のものが無くなったもん
Why do you take it?
なんで取るの?
It's cold though.
寒いんだけど
cold.
冷たい
It's cold.
冷たいよ
寒いもんだって
Your hands are cold, right?
手冷たいでしょ?
cold.
冷たい
Because it's cold, so I'm dressed like this.
だって寒いもん、この格好
Isn't it tough?
きついじゃないかな
It's completely different from your hands.
手と全然違う
I wonder why.
なんでだろうね
I haven't written it.
書いてないよ
Not written?
書いてない?
Not written.
書いてない
It's not sweat, after all.
汗じゃないじゃん、だって
it is.
それは
That's different.
違うじゃん
a little bit.
ちょっと
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
what?
何?
This is it.
これさ
what?
何ですか?
Has it been deleted again?
もう一回消されちゃったの?
why?
なんで?
It would have been better to turn it off.
消したほうがよかった
Just a little.
ちょっとさ
What happened?
どうしたのかな?
It's normal for girls' days to get confused.
普通に女の子の日に ぶれちゃうから
You shouldn't take it that seriously.
そんな にマジマジと見るもんじゃないじゃん
But it's still nice and fresh.
でもまた新鮮でいいね
already.
もう
After all, I've become an adult.
やっぱなんか大人れたわ
Where are you saying it's been a while?
何処に久々って言ってんの
amazing.
すごい
a little bit.
ちょっと
By myself.
自分でさ
I don't always do that.
いつもしてないよ
I always do it.
いつもしてるよ
Don't stare so hard.
あんまじろじろ見ないで
It's not serious.
マジじゃないよ
Because it's not anymore.
もう じゃないから
good?
いい?
Not yet.
まだダメ
Why?
なんでよ
Because it's open.
開いてるから
It's okay.
大丈夫だね
If you step here.
ここに足をのっければ
It's getting dark.
暗くなっちゃったね
It's really messy.
すごいぐしゃぐしゃだね
You must have been cold because you fell asleep.
寝ちゃったから寒かったでしょ
cold.
寒い
This school is cold.
この学校寒い
Come on, come on.
さあさあ
Shall we go get this?
これ入りに行こうか
A little lukewarm.
若干ぬるい
Is it okay if we sleep together because it's cold?
寒いから2人で寝たら大丈夫?
Age
あ げ
It looks like there isn't.
ない ようになってるんだね
what?
な に?
I guess I'm supposed to not give it to you.
あげないようになってるんだね
I agree.
そうだね
I won't give it to you.
ちょっとあげない
It's lukewarm.
ぬるいね
My voice isn't yours.
俺の声、お前じゃないよ
It's a little lukewarm, isn't it?
ちょっとぬるいでしょ
When you get to the bottom, it's quite deep.
下までつくと、 下までつくと、 結構深い
Is this here?
ここある?
There's something.
なんかある
I'll put it in.
入れるから
About the morning, who is this?
朝のこと、 だれこれ?
Bath salts are good, aren't they?
入浴剤いいんだよね
No, what I mean by straight is when you apply this to your skin,
いや、まっすぐとは、 これを肌につけて、
It's good to put it on.
つけるといい
I agree.
そうだね
Just put it in a place where you can hang out at a cafe or something.
カフェとかがつれるやつの、 つければいい
Just put it on.
つければいい
That's because of bubbles.
あれだって、 泡
Bubble?
泡?
It's bubbling.
泡が立ってる
I feel like it doesn't lather because it's not attached properly.
ちゃんとついてないから、 泡立たない気がする
It's not on.
ついてないよね
It's not on, Bubbles.
ついてないよね、泡
Would you like to try it?
入れてみる?
I have it because it's made from drinking, but
飲んでできてるから、 持ってるけど、
I become lazy.
しなしなになっちゃう
That's fine.
いいじゃん
Yeah, it smells good.
うん、いい匂いする
today.
今日
What would be good?
何がいいんだろう
Let's go here.
ここ、 いくよ
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
Look.
見て
amazing.
すごい
It fell.
落ちていった
amazing.
すごい
It's like a dirty stain.
きゃーの汚れみたいな、される
Ah, I see.
あ、そうか
amazing.
すごい
I'm not confused, so it's okay.
迷ってないから、大丈夫
It won't slip.
滑らないよ
Even though it's true, my stomach doesn't slip.
本当だって、 腹が滑らない
slide?
滑る?
It's slipping.
滑るじゃん
dangerous.
危ない
What should I do about this?
これ、どうすればいいの?
picture?
え?
Has it been uploaded?
アップロードなってきた?
Yeah, it's been uploaded.
うん、アップロードなってきた
Yeah, it's been uploaded, but
うん、アップロードなってきたけど、
picture?
え?
Did you have any hobbies like that?
そういう趣味ありましたっけ?
There isn't.
ないよね
Wow, I feel like I'm being shy.
すごい、遠慮してる感じ
Because I've never been there, so I don't know.
だって、一回したことないから、分かんないの
You'll refrain, right?
遠慮するでしょ、そりゃ
What are you going to do?
何にするの?
Hey.
ねえ
What are you going to do?
何にするの?
What should I do?
どうすればいいの?
It's a little bubbling.
ちょっと泡立ってる
Hey.
ねえ
It's coming.
つ いてきてる
Let's go.
すべんだね
Just a little bit.
するする、ちょっと
Hey hey, I'm doing it.
ねえねえ、するするしてる
I'm doing it.
するするしてる
Finish it up, just a little more.
仕上げーよ、もうちょっと
Can you see everyone?
みんな、見えてんの?
Can you see it?
見えてんの?
Are you walking?
歩いてる?
That's how I feel.
そういう気持ちで
I'm being teased.
舐められてるわけよ
picture?
え?
Are you being licked?
舐められてる?
Lick it.
舐めて
oh.
おー
My hands are warm when I lick them.
舐めたら手が温かい
It's open, it's open.
開いてる、開いてる
Take my hand.
手を持って
I'm hungry.
お腹が空いてる
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
I'm hungry.
お腹が空いてる
terrible.
やばい
Isn't this better this time?
今回はこっちの方がいいんじゃない?
I'm hungry.
お腹が空いてる
Okay, this.
いいよ、これ
I'm hungry.
お腹が空いてる
terrible.
やばい
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Yeah, but I thought we'd watch it together later.
そうだけど、 あとで2人で見ようと思った
of.
の
Let's take a look.
見て みよう
I want to sleep, but wait, I can't.
寝るけど、 待って、無理
My legs are up too.
足も起きてる
You're careful, aren't you?
気をしてるのね
I'm going to fall.
落ちちゃう
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
drop down.
落ちる
Good.
よいしょ
what are you doing?
何してるの?
I'm going to fall.
落ちちゃうって
I went to sleep, so wait a minute.
寝たから、ちょっと待って
It's sticky.
ベトベトしてる
Because it was the first.
最初だったから
how was it?
どうだった?
It felt good, but I was tired.
気持ちよかったけど、 疲 れちゃったね
cute.
可愛い
So I'm going to take a break.
ですから、休憩してやるからさ
After this.
この後
Are you hungry?
お腹空いたっしょ?
Take a break.
休憩して
Are you hungry?
お腹空いた?
I might delete it already.
もう消しちゃうかもしれない
There's no side left.
横残ってないよ